<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ProtoCapture</string>
    <string name="hint_proto">Mechanism name</string>

    <!-- Buttons -->
    <string name="create_button">Create</string>
    <string name="button_save">Save</string>
    <string name="edit_button">Edit</string>
    <string name="open_button">Open</string>
    <string name="delete_button">Delete</string>
    <string name="link_button">View Links</string>
    <string name="joint_button">View Joints</string>
    <string name="button_animate">Animate</string>
    <string name="update_button">Update</string>
    <string name="done_button">Done</string>
    <string name="add_button">Add</string>
    <string name="cancel_button">Cancel</string>
    <string name="fix_button">Constrain</string>
    <string name="button_close">Close</string>
    <string name="button_back">Back to Capture</string>

    <!-- Actions -->
    <string name="action_add_joints">Add Joints</string>
    <string name="action_add_links">Add Links</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_run_sim">Run Simulation</string>
    <string name="action_help">Help</string>
    <string name="action_edit_joint">Edit Joint</string>
    <string name="action_view_prototype">View Mechanism</string>
    <string name="action_fix_joints">Constrain Joints</string>
    <string name="action_reset">Reset Sim</string>

    <!-- Labels -->
    <string name="name_label">Name:</string>
    <string name="x_label">**X Coordinate:</string>
    <string name="y_label">**Y Coordinate:</string>
    <string name="constraint_label">Constraint:</string>
    <string name="help_label">Pro Tips:</string>

    <!-- Help Text -->
    <string name="capture_help_text">* Make sure when you tap the screen to pause a frame that every joint you want to select is highlighted with a green circle. Additional circles may be ignored, but you cannot create a joint where a feature has not been highlighted.\n
        * If your joints are not being detected, try darkening them or making them larger. Also try adjusting the lighting.\n
        * If too many features are being detected, try panning out or redrawing your mechanism with lighter lines.\n
        * If you capture a mechanism too zoomed in, it may be difficult to view the simulation later. However, if you are too far out, it may be difficult to add links properly if joints are too close together.\n
        * Select "Add Joints" to add joints to your mechanism. Clicking "Add" makes them permanent. Clicking "Cancel" removes any joints you have just added. Joints can be deleted later.\n
        * Select "Add Links" to combine joints into links. Clicking "Add" makes a single link permanent. Clicking "Done" saves the entire mechanism and takes you to the "View Mechanism" page. Clicking "Cancel" removes any links you have just added. Links can be deleted later.\n
        * When adding links, select the joints in order, beginning and ending with the endpoints.\n</string>

    <string name="simulate_help_text">* Drag a joint to adjust its location and its associated links. It can be slow, so make sure it has caught up before removing your finger. The new location is permanent and will be remembered even if you navigate away from the page.\n
        * Select "Edit Joint" to view the Edit Joint page. You will be able to manually edit a joint\'s location and constraints, as well as its name.\n
        * Select "Constrain Joints" to set the constraint to "fixed" for any joints that you select. You will need to fix joints to fully constrain the mechanism for the simulator to work properly, and the motor joint must be fixed.\n
        * Select "View simulation" to see your mechanism in action! You will be prompted to select a motor joint, which is where the action will be initiated. This is always assumed to be a crank \(circular\) input, and must be a fixed joint.</string>

    <string name="view_help_text">* Select on any link or joint to view and edit its properties. Select "delete" for any link or joint to remove it from the mechanism. Note that deleting a joint will also remove any associated links.\n
        * Select "View Mechanism" to view an image of your captured mechanism, interactively edit it, or see a simulation of your mechanism in action.</string>

</resources>
